<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reeves &amp; Jost Labs</title>
    <link>https://reeveslab.github.io/authors/reeves/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Reeves &amp; Jost Labs</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://reeveslab.github.io/authors/reeves/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://reeveslab.github.io/authors/reeves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reeveslab.github.io/authors/reeves/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Using cutting edge technologies in flow cytometry, RNA sequencing, and -omics tools we are trying to break down and map the fundamental mechanisms behind HIV/SIV resevoir clearance by NK cells and antigen-specific NK cell memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://reeveslab.github.io/authors/keith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reeveslab.github.io/authors/keith/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. R. Keith Reeves is currently Associate Professor of Medicine at Harvard Medical School and the Center for Virology and Vaccine Research (CVVR) of BIDMC.  He is the Director of the Harvard CFAR Advanced Technologies Core, Director of the CVVR Flow Cytometry Core and an Associate Member of the Ragon Institute of MGH, MIT, and Harvard.  He also works within the HIV Vaccine Trials Network (HVTN) and the BEAT-HIV Martin Delaney Cure Collaboratory.  Dr. Reeves obtained his PhD in the laboratory of Dr. Patricia Fultz at the University of Alabama-Birmingham in 2007 where his work focused on plasmacytoid dendritic cells as a mediator of inflammation in lentivirus infections.  Dr. Reeves then completed his postdoctoral work and was junior faculty at the New England Primate Research Center of Harvard Medical School where his studies focused on natural killer (NK) cell biology in nonhuman primates. He has published extensively in this field providing some of the most comprehensive analyses of NK cells and innate lymphoid cells (ILC) in HIV, SIV, and HCV infections to date, including the first characterization of memory NK cells in any primate species. Dr. Reeves’ research, largely supported by individual and consortia grants from NIAID, NIDCR, and amfAR, currently focuses on harnessing NK cells in the context of vaccines and antiviral therapeutics for HIV, CMV and HCV.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
